TorrentCounter.to - Download HD & BluRay Movies in Small Size
Welcome, Mr. Shamsher Singh.
It was really sad to hear
about your dad's sudden demise.
He was a nice man.
Sad...
Sad for what, Mr. Shamsher.
My dad didn't do anything
unusual by dying.
You die...when you got to die.
Please, sit down.
You've raised the security
a notch on the base, Balwinder.
Even the guards are alert.
They even frisked me,
and that too on my own base.
No need to feel bad, Mr. Shamsher.
These people even frisk
me when I come here.
And as for this base...
...you still own this place.
But after you leave...
...this entire property...
...and infrastructure will be mine.
I am all ears, Ballu.
Go on.
From today,
I'll take 20% share of the profits.
And, as a token of my father's
20 years of loyal service...
...you'll have to transfer
this entire property to me.
And, what if I refuse.
Then be prepared to face
losses worth millions of dollars.
You supply arms to all
the biggest countries in the world.
And I know, as well as you...
...how many are licensed,
and how many are unlicensed?
I just have to leak this
information to those countries.
And they will immediately...
...cancel your orders
worth millions of dollars.
You've completely cornered me, Ballu.
I can't let my ego take over and
let your greed shut down my business.
Give me the property papers,
I'll sign them.
Nice pen!
Pier Crown!
Price, only $20,000/-
Do you like it?
Yeah.
Keep it.
You know, Mr. Shamsher Singh.
I never imagined you
would be convinced so easily.
I thought you'll first get angry.
And then, I will have
to convince you in my own way.
But you just agreed.
My older brother used to say.
Any decision when taken in
a fit of rage is never profitable.
So first I took a decision...
...and now I am getting angry.
Very angry!
There's a saying back in my hometown,
in Handia.
"When the lion hunts his prey,
he feeds on it first..."
"...then the vultures
and the scavengers."
"The worms and insects
feeds on the leftovers."
And to me,
you're smaller than an insect.
Shamsher Singh!
Maybe you can control your anger...
...but not me.
And, don't forget that you're unarmed.
You might want to
guarantee your safe return.
Calm down. Calm down.
Those toys which your men
are holding are manufactured by me.
And as for my safe return...
...maybe you're not aware that,
I never do anything without insurance.
Don't try to touch the pen.
It's touch sensitive.
This $20,000 pen is laced
with 20 grams of gelatin.
And the detonator's in my hand.
Tell your men...
...don't even breathe heavily,
and don't move a muscle.
If I press this...
...it will trigger a small
explosion near your heart.
"Poof!"
And it will all be over.
I warned you, Ballu...
...don't mess with this man.
He's dangerous.
For God's sake, do something.
- Hello, sir.
- Cyrus...
Now you will look after the base.
Thank you, sir.
Give the phone to Balwinder.
Hello.
I forgot to mention
a small detail, Ballu.
The deal is off.
'This is Shamsher Singh.'
'He owns the biggest arms
factory on Al Shifa island.'
'25 years ago,
he was accused of manufacturing...'
'...and supplying illegal
arms in his hometown Handia.'
'But he escaped with
his family to this island...'
'...before he could be arrested.'
'Now he operates from here.'
'This is Raghuvendra Sinha,
aka Raghu.'
'Shamsher Singh's
bodyguard And Man-Friday.'
'He's loyal, sharp,
and a man of few words.'
'This is Rana Singha.
Shamsher Singh's arch enemy.'
'He's got his hands in every
illegal business on this planet.'
'He's Powerful...
Evil...
...and Dangerous.'
'Sanjana...
Shamsher Singh's only daughter.'
'Her passion is extreme sports.'
'Also highly trained in
three forms of martial arts.'
'She has got sharp moves,
and a sharper mind.'
'She's bold,
smart, and very ambitious.'
'This is Sanjana's twin-brother,
Suraj Singh.'
'He flies into a rage,
faster than his cars.'
'Which is why his social life completely
depends on the money he splurges.'
'He has a specialty.'
'He acts first and thinks later.'
'This is Yash...'
'Singh family's troubleshooter...'
...and Sikander Singh's close friend,
and body-guard.'
'He's a man of few words,
he speaks and hits more.'
'He's loyal and loveable,
but extremely lethal.'
'And...this is Sikander Singh.'
'Shamsher Singh's step-son...'
'...and, Suraj and
Sanjana's step-brother.'
'He has spent a number of
years in Beijing.'
'After Shamsher Singh,
the most powerful man in this family...'
'...is Sikander Singh.'
'Now you have a brief
on the entire Singh family.'
'And, you know what to do.'
'Let this race begin.'
- Target in sight.
- Good.
Make sure you get him this time.
That's better. You don't worry.
The consignment will
reach you on time.
Raghu, we're in trouble.
They are Rana's men!
Stop! Stop!
Move, Raghu!
Get me closer! Get me closer!
Go left. Left! Left! Left!
Rana sent you, didn't he?
Didn't he?
Yes, Raghu. Tell me.
There's been an assassination
attempt on your dad, Suraj.
What?
- How is dad?
- Now don't worry.
He's safe.
He's with his medical team.
Luckily the bullet
just grazed his shoulder.
Tell me who did this.
Who else can it be other than Rana?
Rana is a dead man.
What was Suraj saying?
He sounded really angry.
I think he's going
to Rana's warehouse.
That boy's an idiot.
I am sure Sanjana's
also gone with him.
Find out...
...where's Sikander.
Sikander's been already informed.
This always came to my
aide when I was in trouble.
And it's one of the
closest thing to my heart.
My lucky mascot.
And now it's yours.
Really?
Thank you.
She's beautiful.
Keep it.
Sexy uncle,
you must be feeling a little jealous.
Actually,
he must be feeling very jealous.
Not jealous, I am happy.
I had my eyes on it.
But you deserve it.
Thank you.
Raghu,...
...tell Suraj and Sanjana
to meet me in my den.
And find out how far
our lawyer has reached?
Welcome, my lawyer friend. Welcome.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
- I hope you're okay.
- Nothing, just a...scratch.
Did you recognize him?
He's our family lawyer.
- Srikant Verma.
- Hello.
- Hi, sir.
Come.
Where do you think you two are going?
Sit down.
He's here especially for you two.
- Any tea/coffee, Srikant?
- No.
Thank you, sir.
Then shoot, Lawyer.
A few weeks ago,
you two celebrated your 25th birthday.
So I am here to execute
your mother's will.
Ohhh...
Nice.
Your mother, Sumitra Devi...
...divided her property
of Al Shifa in two parts.
She gave 50% of this
property to Sikander...
...which I already transferred
in his name a few years ago.
And she transferred 50% to you two...
...and, the time has come to execute it.
25% each.
So here's the Will...
...and, I'll need your
signatures here, son.
- Do I sign here?
- Yes.
Congratulations, children.
Now you two are 50%
partners of this property.
Okay sir, I'll take your leave.
See you soon.
- Thank you, sir.
- See you, sir.
- Bye.
What was this, bro?
Like seriously?
We get 25% each,
while he gets 50.
Really dad.
Even mom treated us the same way
you've have been treating us.
Are we your children, or is he?
You are my children,...
...and so is he.
Your cousin.
Sikander's like your brother.
When did this happen, dad?
He's my older brother...
...Rannchod Singh's son.
'27 years ago,
we owned a small arms factory...'
'...in our hometown of Handia,
in Allahabad.'
'The arms we made in this factory...'
'...were only supplied
to the Indian Army.'
'Handia's local politician,
Gajendra Pathak...'
'...and his son Narender,...
...wanted us to illegally
supply them weapons.'
'I've said this before,...
...I will never do anything illegal.'
- Goodbye.
- 'But my brother refused to comply...'
'...and we ended up
making them our enemies.'
Do you know who you're talking to?
- I'll set this place ablaze.
- Shamsher...
Shamsher.
'This incident also
took a toll on our family.'
'Sumitra,
who loved her son Sikander a lot...'
'...was very concerned.'
'A week later our arms consignment
was being transported by road.'
'We rode with the trucks...'
'...because we had information
that Gajender was planning...'
'...to hi-jack our trucks.'
'And that's exactly what happened.'
'His men had us surrounded.'
'We ended up killing Gajender's
son in that encounter.'
'Son's death drove Gajender crazy.'
'Gajender swore to ruin our family.'
'And his first target was my brother.'
'But, this feud didn't
end with my brother's demise.'
'Gajender used his
power and influence...'
'...to prove that we
supply arms to terrorists.'
'Our factory was sealed.'
'We were deemed as traitors.'
'And our entire family's
life was in danger.'
'I immediately sent Sikander
to Beijing with Raghu.'
'And I came to Al Shifa
along with Sumitra.'
'My brother had already bought
a small island out here...'
'...in order to expand his business.'
With my hard work,
I started an arms factory out here.
I took Sumitra under my refuge according
to our family's rites and rituals.
And married her.
A year later you two were born.
Sumitra's health started to
deteriorate after you two were born.
And soon she passed away.
If we hadn't killed Gajendra's
son in a fit of rage...
...then we would still
be living in our country.
But I promise you...
If you two are with me...
...then soon we'll return to our home.
We'll go back to Handia.
And live together
once again like family.
They are gone,
it had no effect on them.
They will change.
What the hell is happening, bro?
- What happened?
- Nothing...
First mom gave 50% of
her property to Sikander.
And now dad wants
to go back to Handia.
Who wants to go to Handia, man?
Calm down, Suraj.
I was angrier than you
after hearing mom's will.
But I controlled myself.
And whenever dad praises
that Sikander,...
- ...my blood boils.
- I swear.
But, I don't show it.
And, if you want to
solve this problem for good...
...then Sikander must never get a
whiff of what's cooking in our minds.
I hope you can do that much, Suraj.
Of course, bro.
- Good.
- Of course.
"Come a little closer,
and hold my hand..."
"Walk with me,
and just sit there."
"And share your
thoughts with me, baby..."
"Just for once be selfish, baby,
and live for yourself."
Wow... very nice, bravo.
- Thank you.
- Cheers.
Cheers, bro.
- Lovely, lovely.
- Cheers, Sikku bro.
- Oh my, God.
- What happened?
- We're all such big losers.
- Why, bro?
- We have everything we need.
- This?
Correct. We have everything we need.
But we don't have what they have.
Yeah man.
...everybody has a girlfriend.
Bro, they are all in love.
Shame on us.
Not all of us.
- Just the three of you.
- What?
Meaning I met a girl a few days ago...
- Really?
- And I've fallen in love with her.
And soon she'll be coming over,
at their party.
It's a done deal.
- Signed, sealed, and delivered.
- Really.
With a kiss.
- Yes. Cheers.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
Happy for you, bro.
Why are you so sad?
Don't you have a
beautiful girlfriend too?
I did.
Again?
Yash, I've got to do
something about my temper.
I scared her.
It wasn't your temper that scared her.
It was your face.
That's really mean Sikku bro.
Chill, bro. I am there.
That's my sister. That's my sister.
Come here.
I saw that.
It's just not my day today.
You three have raised
the bar so high...
...that they all
look like idiots to me.
I agree.
The day I find that boy...
...I'll go straight to dad.
And tell him I am in love.
Then get married.
Have couple of children.
And I am done.
Cheers.
- Cheers.
- Cheers, bro.
Come on.
Tell us.
Well, since everyone is
talking their heart out...
...so let me share
my experience as well.
- Hold on. Bro...guitar.
- Why?
Background music is important.
- There you go, bro.
- Exactly.
- Really?
- Of course.
Go on.
So, during my time in Beijing...
...I saw this gorgeous girl.
Beautiful.
Where are you?
I've been waiting for half an hour.
What... You're ditching.
Bye.
Indian!
Be careful...
She's Indian.
We love India.
Best of luck then.
- Hey...what are you drinking?
- Sorry...do I know you?
No?
- We'll get to know.
- No thanks.
Okay listen,
you guys need to leave right now.
No, seriously.
I don't want to make a scene,
But I will call security.
- Lovely...
- Please leave.
Don't touch me.
- God...
- Goodbye.
Hello.
Hello...and thank you.
You are very welcome.
Ahh-Ahh... excuse me...
So now you're going
to officially hit on me.
Men are all the same.
Explain me this to me.
Three guys come over,
they praise you...
...but, you don't like that.
An Indian comes to a
fellow Indian's rescue.
But you don't like that either.
- Isn't that kind of...
- Wa...wa...wait!
Weird.
Weird! Yes, weird.
I was born weird.
Oh.. I like that.
So why don't you tell me
where you were born, what time...
...and what for? What's the purpose?
So that when I have kids,
I will avoid all these things totally.
You are so weird.
- Thank you.
- That's not a compliment.
Really.
I am weird.
Bye, weirdo.
Oh no.
Are you following me?
Following you...
- I came down this aisle...
- Weirdo.
"I'll never...stop following you,
sweetheart..."
Listen, this is too much.
I guess I'll have
to call the security.
I...
You know, sweetheart.
This is a very common coincidence.
This two-bedroom suite belongs to me...
...and, that common room belongs to you.
Yeah, right.
I am so stupid!
Yeah...
...very stupid.
Can you hear me?
Actually no...
I am trying to guess
what you're going to say next.
Sorry.
Fine. These things happen.
I understand.
By the way...
...my name is Sikander.
Sikander Singh.
I am Jessica.
Nice to meet you, Jessica.
Nice to meet you, Sikander.
"Our sights, and our breath..."
"...met when we met."
"Let's forget the past...
...and think about
now and the future."
"Nobody knows what
the future holds for us."
"Let's give it our best."
"Sweetheart..."
"When we're close..."
"...when we're together..."
"...when we're face to face..."
"...my soul wants to say..."
"I found love..."
"I found it in you!"
"Because I found love..."
"I found love..."
"I found it in you!"
"Because I found love..."
"I found love..."
"I found it in you!"
"It's a good thing that I got to..."
"...know about your flaws,
before your qualities."
"It's really amazing..."
"It's truly amazing, that..."
"...that I fell in love
with your flaws as well."
"Oh, baby..."
"When we're close..."
"...when we're together..."
"...when we're face to face..."
"...my soul wants to say..."
"I found love..."
"I found it in you!"
"Because I found love..."
"I found love..."
"I found it in you!"
"I've entrusted my life...
my life..."
"...in your hands, and in your eyes."
"I've found my way to your heart,
through your lips."
"Without worrying about the future..."
"...let's live life
as it comes our way."
"Because I found love..."
"I found love..."
"I found it in you!"
"Because I found love..."
"I found love..."
"I found it in you!"
"Because I found love..."
"I found love..."
"I found it in you!"
Oh my, God.
Sikander Singh is in love.
- What happened then?
- Then...
I waited for a couple of days.
Then I waited for another week.
And then I found out...
...that she's disappeared.
Awww...
I feel ya, bro.
I felt it too, bro.
I found my true love.
So I'll pray that
you soon find yours, bro.
What the... it's Birju.
Brij my friend.
Where are you?
How are you?
I am absolutely fine, Shamshu.
- I just landed in your city.
- So why call?
Drop by at my mansion.
I came all the way here to meet you.
But this matter is a little sensitive.
I've booked room no.
1001 at the Intercontinental hotel.
1001... understand.
Can you meet me in an hour?
It's really urgent.
I can get there before you and
welcome you personally with flowers.
- Just say the word.
- Then get there immediately.
Great. See you in one hour.
"Sweety..."
- Shamshu...
- Brijwa...
- It's been 10 long years, Brij.
- Yes.
But you haven't changed at all.
Enough praising me,
and look at yourself.
You still look dashing-fantastic.
If you stand outside
Mishra's dairy even now...
...girls will
fall head over heels for you.
Don't talk about home,
it's depressing.
What's the job?
Shamshu, you know that my boss,
Johnny Srivastav...
...owns a 7-star hotel in Manali.
I do... It's really amazing.
But you don't know
what goes on in that hotel.
The top politicians and businessmen
of India patronize that hotel.
Not because it's exclusive.
But because it's the center
for every kind of debauchery.
- Brothel.
- Yes, a brothel.
And only a handful
of VIPs know about it.
This place offers every
kind of sexual perversion.
But these politicians didn't know...
...that Johnny had installed
multiple spy-cams in every room.
And he would record their indulgence.
Only Johnny and I knew this secret.
But somehow this
information was leaked...
...and Rana found out about it.
A few days ago Johnny
came to Al Shifa for a deal.
But Rana's men kidnapped him.
Rana's men started torturing Johnny...
...and wanted to know
where the hard disk was.
Poor Johnny would've
told them everything anyway...
...but he died of a sudden heart attack.
- The guy's heart shut down.
- Hmmm...
- Due to the torture.
- Yes.
And where are the videos?
The videos are on this hard disk.
If we can get our
hands
on this hard disk...
...then you can't imagine
the possibilities.
Oh, my...
Yash, did you see this?
Dad, this is mind-boggling.
It's a gold mine.
But where is this hard disk?
The hard disk is locked away in locker
no. 7003 of the SRL Bank in Cambodia.
All you have to do
is steal that hard disk.
Wow... you're a true friend.
You told me about the bank
and locker before naming your price.
Great...just great.
I know its great
But the disk is password
protected, Shamshu.
And only I know the password.
The password panel is touch
Sensitive and pressure sensitive too.
So it's very important for me to
be alive while entering the password.
Yeah...
That's even better.
"Sweety..."
Son, Brij wants $1
billion in bearer bonds...
...and $1 billion by cheque.
We must speak with
the banker for a loan.
And Interpol Officer Khanna
will blackmail the politicians for us.
$2 billion!
1 billion officially,
and 1 billion in bearer bonds.
All for a hard disk.
And we're resorting to blackmail.
Through that Interpol officer Khanna.
That sleazy Khanna.
Sleazy deal.
I don't understand the motive
and outcome of this deal.
What did you say?
Waste of time.
Waste of time?
Though you studied at Oxford...
...but, you don't have
even an ounce of brain.
He wants to know
the motive and result...
I would've even paid
him $10 billion for it.
I would've sold everything to pay him.
What do we have out here?
What is this?
No one supports me.
Not even my own throat.
What are you looking at? Do your job.
Get those two damn boxes here.
Sit...
My intention is to clear
your father's and my name...
...which was discredited years ago.
And the result will be
that we'll be able to return home...
...to Handia, with pride.
That's the motive and the result.
I accepted this job
because I have faith in you.
I promise you...
...that I'll risk my life
to get that hard disk for you.
So that I can send you back
to your home in Handia with pride.
I am really homesick, son.
Just send me back home.
So that I may never need
Restyl and Calmpose again.
"Sweety..."
- Welcome. Welcome.
- Hello.
- Greetings.
Nice party, Raghu.
What's the occasion?
Mr. Khanna has arrived.
- Yeah...yeah...
- Excuse me, sir.
Officer Khanna has arrived.
These are our politicians.
They have stooped so low.
They can do anything for debauchery.
And officers like us
take orders from them, sir.
Shameless people.
Some of them, Khanna.
They give a bad name
to all the politicians.
But I must admit, sir.
This hard disk is like a guided
Missile from Al Shifa to India.
And you will launch this missile.
Raghu will give you
soft copies after the party.
And I'll tell you
what to do with them.
$1 billion... it's a big amount.
- For you, Mr. Goel.
- Yes...
Yes...
It must be a pretty big business deal.
Sorry, sir.
We don't tolerate anyone
interfering in our business.
Our business is our business.
None of your business.
It can take some time.
And Singh sir, you might have
to give some collateral for this loan.
Obviously...
Don't let me catch you again.
Yes... Sorry, sir.
Jessica, you're already here.
I can't believe my eyes.
How can I break your trust?
And you should know me by now.
I never break a promise
or a commitment.
Oh... the man himself. My hero.
He's the guy I work for.
He's like a brother to me.
Sikander Singh.
Hi, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
And, Suraj. My boss' son.
Hi, very nice to meet you.
Hi...nice to meet you.
- You sing too?
- A little... Why?
No, they are twins,
and that's their cousin.
And yes, they are all Singhs.
- Hi, Sanjana Singh.
- Hi. Nice to meet you.
Oh my, God. She's so pretty.
Yeah, she is.
By the way, where did you meet her?
Even I would like to know this.
Jealous?
- Yes...
I am happy.
Come on, let's have some drinks.
A round of shots for everybody.
Cheers, bro.
Go, Yash.
"Weekend parties are on..."
"You and me..."
"...we're together,
and a tattoo on our arm."
"Weekend parties are on..."
"You and me..."
"...we're together,
and a tattoo on our arm."
"These bling-bling lights."
"And the super funky night."
"Let things unfold the way they want..."
"...we've got all the right."
"Let the party go on-and-on."
"Let the party go on-and-on-and-on..."
"The stars are shining bright..."
"...just let yourself lose tonight."
"Everything is looking so beautiful..."
"...so come a little closer."
"The intoxication in the air..."
"...is getting me high."
"I just touched it with my hands..."
"...to believe its right."
"We've been slightly
boozing all night."
"And everything is looking bright."
"Let things unfold the way they want..."
"...we've got all the right."
"Let the party go on-and-on."
"Let the party go on-and-on-and-on..."
"Everybody party hard."
"We're going to dance all night."
"Don't stop drinking
till you're high."
"Take my advice..."
"...we're gonna keep drinking..."
"...and won't stop until we drop."
"Let's go baby on the floor."
"Let me love you more and more."
"Your love's spreading
through the air."
"Your spell's drawing
me closer and closer."
"As I let my guard down..."
"...I lost my heart."
"There's definitely some connection..."
"...that I found you."
"We're together tonight."
"Everything is gonna be alright."
"Let things unfold the way they want..."
"...we've got all the right."
"Let the party go on-and-on."
"Let the party go on-and-on-and-on..."
Olga, it was so nice to see you.
- I am going to call you, okay.
- Yes.
Drive carefully, okay.
- See you, then.
- Love you, baby.
- Bye.
Sikander played it well.
Careful with him.
Guy's out cold.
He can't even handle too much booze.
How will he handle Jessica?
Exactly, Sanju.
Listen...you look really happy.
I am... but, nothing's confirmed yet.
Let me confirm,
and I'll let you know in the morning.
Ohh...
After you. Come, sis.
Hi.
Hello, weirdo.
Why do you want to meet someone...
...you don't even trust
or have faith in?
You're still angry.
He's a great guy.
Yash.
When did you meet him?
When or how, or what's
my relationship with him...
that's none of your business.
You've no right to
ask these questions.
And, if I'd known
that you're Yash' boss...
...then I would've never come here.
You were such a jerk.
You're right, I was a jerk.
I made a big mistake.
I am really sorry, Jessica.
I tried to find you after that day.
Yeah, right.
Come on.
I am sorry.
It's over.
Jessica...
I know I went overboard last night.
And I am sorry about it.
That's not the point, Yash.
Just leave it alone.
Try to understand, Yash.
Jessica.
Keys, please.
- Stop acting like a child now.
- You grow up.
- Yash. Jessica.
- Oh god!
Going somewhere?
Not me, she is.
- To stay at the Marriott.
- Marriott.
Why? Any special reason?
I am not comfortable here.
- Here?
- Yes...
Ohhh...
I wouldn't want to interfere
between boyfriend and girlfriend.
Your thing.
- Congratulations on the girlfriend.
- Thank you.
- Bye, Yash.
- Enjoy.
- Bye.
- Jessica.
Look at them...
how they've grown up.
But when will they mature?
Brij must be waiting for
the bonds at the Intercontinental.
You go, Sikander.
Yes...
Great.
Good.
Nonsense. I don't believe this.
And you shouldn't.
Anyone who believes in
hear-says are very gullible.
And you're not that
kind of a guy, Yash.
You run around that Sikku all day.
You even took a bullet for him, Yash.
And now he's making a fool out of you.
Bro, this time open your laptop,
and not your heart...
...and show him proof.
- Then he will believe you.
- Sure.
Wait, wait, wait.
I want to see that hug again.
What passion, bro. What passion.
I can understand the hug.
Even friends hug.
But smooch.
Yash, hi.
Where are you going, Yash?
Yash, come back here.
Yash!
What's wrong, Yash?
What are you doing?
Yash!
What are you doing, ya...
God!
Yash.
- Where is he?
- Yash.
- Listen to me.
Where is he?
- Yash, please.
- Here I am.
Right here, Yash.
Right here.
Yash.
How could you do this to me, man?
How could you do this to me?
Relax.
Relax?
Sikander.
Every coin has two sides.
On one side is my dear friend...
...and on the other side is the girl.
But remember...
Nothing comes before
family and loyalty.
You're 100% right, Yash.
100% right.
But in this situation...
Girl.
But you're so shocked, that
you're starting to sound very preachy.
Now listen to what I have to say.
Every coin has two sides.
Two...
But this one has four...
She's the same Jessica
I met in Beijing.
Six months before she met you.
What do you think?
She just fell in our lap?
A miracle?
You think this is a coincidence.
I said stop it.
- This beautiful...
- I said stop it, Sikander.
- Please.
- Jessica...
...this is between brothers.
I can't lie to him.
And Jessica, when the foundation
of any relationship is based on a lie...
...how's that bloody ever going to work.
And you think I betrayed you.
For what?
For a girl?
Do you want to know the truth?
Forget it.
Bring it on.
Then listen...
That morning when I woke up,
I found a note left by Jessica.
It said;
"He babe, I am going to
be out for a couple of days".
"Something urgent has come up."
"I will call you. Love, Jessi."
When I went back for my laptop...
...I noticed that my
bag of money was missing.
I found Jessica's air
ticket from the dustbin.
- Yes?
- You will have to come with us.
Thank God you're here.
There's been some confusion.
They think I've stolen something.
Is she the one?
Unfortunately.
- I didn't steal anything.
- Ma'am, please...
Sikander.
- Please, ma'am.
- You know me.
- And when I returned to the hotel.
- Excuse me.
Excuse me, sir.
I believe this is yours.
Please check the contents.
Our security team apprehended
one of our junior staff's with it.
I am really sorry,
sir, for the inconvenience.
- Was there a female involved with him?
- No, sir. He was working alone.
- Thank you.
- Sorry, sir.
So Jessica didn't steal the bag.
She's very complicated.
After the lady was arrested,
I went back to my hotel room.
Feeling like crap.
I thought of doing some
investigation on my own.
Since you can't even trust love,
how can you trust anyone in business?
You know that I always hide a spy cam
with all my documents and money.
When I saw the spy cam,
imagine what is see.
Jessica, in a green top and red pant...
So Jessica stole the bag.
Yes...
But then I realized something.
Her beautiful hands weren't
the only ones involved.
- I went down to the Police station...
- Let's go.
...and bailed her out.
Thank you.
Listen to me.
I don't want to hear anything.
You suspected me.
How could you?
And I...
And I thought our
relationship was special.
- I never want to see your face again...
- Please be quiet, Jessica.
Stop this charade.
Over-bloody-acting.
I know you stole the bag.
So, weirdo, you met me
under very unusual circumstances.
Very nice.
And I just couldn't help
but fall in love with you.
Then another situation was created...
...where I doubt you,...
And I am proven wrong.
And I feel like crap.
If I hadn't hidden a spy cam...
...then I would still
be feeling like crap.
Now I just want to know one thing.
You did everything willingly,
and why?
I don't know why I was asked
to do this, nor did I ask.
When the money is that good,
why ask questions?
Who hired Jessica?
Suraj and Sanjana.
I must admit they
have a wicked mind.
I know.
But why are they doing all this?
They want us to butt heads.
Which is why in the security
room we showed the twins...
...what they wanted to see.
But Yash, you must tell them that...
...all the misunderstandings
between us have been cleared now.
And Sikander has promised
never to interfere between us.
You must clear another
misunderstanding between us.
Whose side are you on?
I am sorry, Yash.
Yours.
It's cool.
But what is their plan?
I don't know.
Those two fools are trying
to eliminate me from this race...
...but they don't know that the
'Champion' of this race... is me!
So ladies and gentlemen,
as you all know...
...the whole world has
declared a war on drugs.
According to our
recent Interpol reports...
...the drug industry has taken over...
Excuse me...
Hello.
You must be really busy, Khanna.
I called you a couple of times.
But you didn't answer.
Sorry, Shamsher sir,
I was busy in a conference.
But please go ahead.
I've texted you the
names of eight politicians.
- You know what to do.
- Consider it done, sir.
Great. Great.
Speak to you later.
Raghu, one joker,
and eight politicians.
Now watch how this
joker turns the tables.
Hello.
Mr. Chauhan,
this is officer Khanna from Interpol.
Interpol?
It's evident from
these photos and videos...
...how sensitive is this situation...
These photos and videos
shouldn't leak out at any cost.
I am willing to pay any price.
I've been instructed
to tell you that...
...you must come to
Al Shifa in a few days.
The deal for these photos
and videos will go down there.
Okay... Okay, I will be there.
Who do I have to meet?
The place and time
will be texted to you.
Hello... Hello...
Oh my, God.
Napkin.
What's wrong with you, Yash?
Nothing, it's just that Sikander...
I mean I was thinking about Jessica.
Think, Yash, think.
In fact, that's all you can
do for the rest of your life now.
You got yourself a
girlfriend and her ex-lover.
In a package deal.
It's not funny, Suraj.
Sikander has promised he
won't come between Jessica and me.
And you believed him.
Bro, Yash is so naive.
There are two point
of views to see this situation.
A male and a female.
The male point of view.
Sikander knew that
you're serious about Jessica.
Still he called Jessica
to the security room at 2 am.
Why?
And if Jessica and
you ever get married...
...you'll never be able
to get those two out of your head.
And if that happens,
which I think it will...
...what will you do then?
There's nothing you can do, Yash.
Because Sikander's your bro,
your mentor, he's everything for you.
Including your wife's lover.
Jealous.
- Now... the female point of view.
- Enough!
What do I do, dammit?
- What do I do?
- Simple...
Quit 'team Sikander'
and join 'team Twins'.
We're willing to offer you
10% partnership in our business...
...and Jessica will be 100% yours.
How much is that?
110%
So, Mr. Yash,
the ball is in your court.
Bro...
Here's the layout of the
municipal plans for this area.
You book the nightclub...
...and I'll go open an account.
Please come, sir.
Once again thank you so much, sir...
...for opening a big
account in our bank.
- You're welcome.
- Please come.
This is your locker.
Please take your time.
- Thank you so much, sir.
- Thank you.
Sexy uncle, see you later alligator.
See you.
Did you sell your loyalty?
Forget 10%, I wouldn't join hands
with them even for 100%
But if someone tries to buy
me with love, then that's different.
They don't make men like you anymore.
What is their modus operandi?
They have a wicked mind.
Didn't tell me anything.
It's in our genes.
Runs in our blood.
And every inch of our body.
In the entire family.
Sir, Sikku and everyone else must
be waiting in the premiere room...
...we called them at 12 sharp.
Coming, Raghu, coming.
And the blind school people
are here for the donation.
Just fill in the name.
Yes, Khanna, what's the update?
Shamsher sir...
You let a cat loose amongst pigeons.
All the politicians
are ready for a meeting.
Great.
So we meet exactly after 8 days.
Yes, sir.
So...
The street layout of the
SRL bank is on this digital screen.
Okay.
Uncle, I've only one condition.
This heist will be only
carried out by family.
Better, much better.
Correct, dad.
Family members will do it together.
Yeah, bro.
We'll steal the hard
disk on Saturday night.
This is SRL Bank,
and here's the basement.
Sorry, dad. I am hungry.
The locker room's in
the basement of the SRL bank.
The hard disk is in locker no. 7003.
There's a nightclub
adjacent to the bank.
There's a drainage that
connects the nightclub...
...and this bank's wall.
Sorry!
Suraj, Sanjana, Yash.
You three will arrive in Cambodia
on Saturday night by flight.
Here you'll find a yellow van
in the airport's parking lot.
Yellow van, guys.
How tacky.
Twins, just hear him out, guys.
We are listening.
And Yash, we are born winners.
Even if you two run alone in a race,
you'll still come second.
Understand?
And I'll arrive in
Cambodia by helicopter.
Give me your hand please.
Don't worry,
I am not proposing to you.
That hurts.
Good.
Please...
Doesn't matter, your loss.
- This is a micro-fluid tracking device.
- Show me.
Through this, we can track each other.
Micro-fluid tracking device.
Nonsense.
Think twice before
you ask for my hand again.
I guess Cambodia's getting to you.
Your humor's getting better
- Weirdo.
- Let's go.
Come on, guys.
Let's go.
Yash. Come in, Yash.
Yes, Sikku.
Come on, guys.
It's show time.
"I couldn't stop
thinking about you..."
"...I've never seen
anyone like you."
"I couldn't stop
thinking about you..."
"...I've never
seen anyone like you."
"Sweetheart..."
"Sweetheart...
since I got high on you..."
"...you can't imagine
what it's done to me."
"Sweetheart...
since I got high on you..."
"...your beloved's
completely ruined."
- "You blow my mind."
- "...your beloved's completely ruined."
"Sweetheart...
since I got high on you..."
"...you can't imagine
what it's done to me."
- "You blow my mind."
- "...your beloved's completely ruined."
"I've been thinking about you."
"I'm always lost in your thoughts..."
"It's your fault that I keep
saying this over and over again."
"I'm always lost in your thoughts..."
"It's your fault that I keep
saying this over and over again."
"I want to keep chanting your name..."
"...until the moon keeps
shining over the horizon."
"Sweetheart..."
"Sweetheart...
since I was floored by you..."
"...you can't imagine
what it's done to me."
"Sweetheart...
since I got high on you..."
"...your beloved's completely ruined."
- "You blow my mind."
- "...your beloved's completely ruined."
"Your beloved..."
"My day starts with you,
and ends too."
"Even All the books
can't describe you."
"You quietly stole my heart."
"Stole my sleep and
kept me awake at nights.
"You quietly stole my heart."
"Stole my sleep and
kept me awake at nights.
"Sweetheart..."
"Sweetheart...
since I got lost in your eyes..."
"...you can't imagine
what it's done to me."
"Sweetheart...
since I got high on you..."
"...your beloved's completely ruined."
- "You blow my mind."
- "...your beloved's completely ruined."
"I've been thinking about you."
Let's go.
See you later.
No... Help me, please...
Move.
Come fast.
Dad.
Suraj.
Your hard disk.
God job.
I knew I could trust Sikander.
Great. Great.
Let's have a party tomorrow.
Sure, dad.
I'll get it organized.
Where are the others?
Sikku's taking the long way home.
He'll arrive tomorrow evening.
And as for Yash and Sanjana.
They will be here
in a couple of hours.
Whose calling? Jessica?
Dad's calling.
Dad?
Yes... your dad.
He's trying to make a video call.
Should I answer it?
Dad and all, huh.
Why don't you tell him about us first?
I know.
I feel bad about it.
Once we're out of this stress...
...then I'll talk to Suraj and dad.
I love you, Yash.
What are you thinking?
You know what...
The way you pulled
off this entire plan...
I am shocked.
Why?
A; You planted Jessica
in Sikander's life.
B; On your instructions, she told
Sikander that Suraj and I planted her.
And the best part...
C; That smart-alec got
so engrossed in all this,...
...that he never suspected about you.
Genius, huh!
Rana? Why is he calling you?
Chill, Sanjana.
In our business,
the fewer the enemies we have...
...the more our business grows.
Cambodia is Rana's fortress.
I can have Sikander
killed right there.
But your mother's Will saved him.
Mother's will?
There's a clause which states that...
...if any one of you dies
an unnatural death,...
...then his share will go to charity.
- Oh no.
- And I can't let that happen.
But there's only one
thing that's bothering me.
Jessica. She knows everything.
Jessica. Jessica.
How much do you make in
a year by conning people?
$300,000.
I'll give you one million.
What's the job?
Two things.
One, you must do exactly as I say.
Second, no questions.
That's it?
Deal.
Job over, game over.
Do I even know you, Yash?
I always thought of you
as a very loyal and honest man.
I am...
...but only for us.
Nowadays, if you want
to live on your own terms...
...you got to be a little selfish.
"Come closer and hold my hands."
"Walk with me and sit with me."
"And share your thoughts with me."
"Just once, baby,
be selfish and live for yourself."
"Don't ever...think..."
"...that I am misleading you."
"I know...that I am..."
"...no one to you."
"But you've done...
done so much for me."
"And I have a right
to be selfish for... you."
"Just once baby,
be selfish and live for yourself."
"There's a smile...on your face."
"But why are your eyes...moist?"
"I am very happy..."
"...and yet...
there's something lacking."
"Let's fill this void forever."
"Let's rely on each other."
"Just once baby,
be selfish and live for yourself."
- Hello.
- Captain.
I smell some good news.
No worries,
he will be here for 50 years.
And if you want,
I can kill him right now.
No, no. Let him stay alive.
- Soon you'll get the rest of your money.
- Okay.
God protects you...
...and keeps you from all harm.
Explaining.
Now this.
What happened?
God protects you and
keeps you from all harm.
What?
Explaining.
Catch him.
Take your positions. Catch them.
There. There.
Shoot him.
Take him out.
Shoot him. Shoot him.
Take him out. Shoot him.
- Catch him.
- Close the gate. Close the gate.
- Stop him.
Stop him.
Chase him. Chase him.
Everybody fire, go now.
Perfect timing.
If it wasn't for me...
Then it would've been someone else.
- Idiot.
- Oh no.
Sorry.
What?
It's okay.
So many obstacles and hurdles.
When is this going to end, man?
These hurdles and are
a part of the race of life.
They start before we're born.
But don't end after we die.
Too deep. Bouncer.
In short...
I won't spare those rascals...
...Whoever is bloody
responsible for this.
Oh no.
Do I have to dress you up as well?
Suit up. Wear your gear.
Need some help.
- Thanks.
- Watch out.
Okay, all set.
Cheers.
"We're coming back to the race."
"You've pushed me too far away..."
"...concealing all
the lies in your heart."
"This comes straight
from my wounded heart."
"Wait and watch what's
coming for you."
"This fake love...
is your nature."
"Every time...
you kept betraying me."
"Your intoxication...
is intoxicating."
"Lord hear my plea..."
"...my life's in danger again."
"This time its certain doom."
"In your love."
"Lord hear my plea..."
"...my life's in danger again."
"This time its certain doom."
"In your love."
"Lord hear my plea..."
"...my life's in danger again."
"This time its certain doom."
"In your love."
"Life has brought you
to a crossroad again."
"Soon you'll be free
from the bonds of this world."
"You'll pay for your crimes."
"I'll never spare you,
nor will the Lord."
"You're my obsession,
my intoxication, and my desire."
"My fascination is to get rid of you."
"There's no way for you to run..."
"...I have my eyes on you."
"I want to ruin you,
and that's my resolution."
"Your intoxication...is intoxicating."
"Lord hear my plea..."
"...my life's in danger again."
"This time its certain doom."
"In your love."
"Lord hear my plea..."
"...my life's in danger again."
"This time its certain doom."
"In your love."
"Life on the line..."
"We hold it down..."
"They tired to break us...
We never let'em.."
"We never let'em.."
"Just you and I..."
"It's do or die.."
"Ready forever"
"We run this race race..."
"Can't stop it, can't slow it down.."
"We living for the chase chase.."
"Hey we're on the run..."
Ain't got no time for to waste"
"We run this race race..."
"Life on the line..."
"We hold it down..."
"They tired to break us...
We never let'em.."
"We never let'em.."
"Just you and I..."
"It's do or die.. Ready forever"
"Ready forever"
"Celebrate all you want tonight."
"Tomorrow you're mine."
"Drink till you drop."
"The race begins again."
"And you better concentrate."
"Enjoy all you want, because..."
"We're coming back to the race."
"Lord hear my plea..."
"...my life's in danger again."
"This time its certain doom."
"In your love."
"Lord hear my plea..."
"...my life's in danger again."
"This time its certain doom."
- "In your love."
- "We're coming back to the race."
What am I hearing, Suraj?
I don't know, dad. I swear.
This is ridiculous.
We're not responsible for whatever
happened with brother in Cambodia.
And what's her name...
Yeah, Jessica.
What's this Jessica angle?
There is no angle, dad.
I can't figure out who puts
this filth in Sikander's mind?
Okay, Suraj.
You try to hide it your way...
...and I'll find out my way.
And if turns out to be true...
...then you'll have to answer for it.
And then I'll deal with it.
Deal with what, dad?
Do you even see us?
I mean you can't see beyond
your blue-eyed boy Sikander.
Sikku.
Who will run the business?
Who will look after
the administration?
Sikku.
Who's the smartest and
most intelligent amongst us?
Sikku.
I am sick of this Sikku, dad.
But enough is enough.
What's on your mind?
What do you want?
- Split.
- Split?
We'll handle the business...
...he can take his share and leave.
We've no problem. But...
...for good.
You two will handle the business.
You two?
Exactly, dad.
You always underestimate us.
What?
Underestimate?
I didn't expect this from you two.
Expectations.
Dad, you shouldn't be
talking about expectations.
I know what's good and what's bad.
And as long as I am alive,
there will be no split.
Don't be so difficult, dad.
Like you always said...
Love grows when you share.
I do...
Love grows when you share,
but not split.
But dear...
You could neither learn
our language nor the emotion.
I trust Sikander completely.
And until this deal isn't sealed,
you two won't mess things up.
Is that clear?
- Sure, dad.
- Yes, dad.
Mr. Goel called from the bank.
He's sanctioned the
loan against our property.
You three will sign
the bank documents.
Goodnight.
Sad. Very sad.
Unfortunately...
There's no cure for stupidity.
What's the matter, uncle?
You're still awake.
Thinking about home?
Shall I get Calmpose
or Restyl for you?
You're my Restyl and Calmpose.
Come, nephew.
Walk with me.
I never imagined those
two hated you so much.
What should I do with
this bloody power and money?
Should I shove it up my...locker.
Now I am completely determined.
I just want to seal this
deal and go back to Handiya.
This deal isn't going anywhere, uncle.
But can I give you an advice.
You handled this
matter completely wrong.
If you give so much love and always
be partial to me in front of them...
...then obviously,
those two are bound to hate me.
You're absolutely right, Sikku.
I wish I had realized this earlier...
...then my family
would've never split up.
This family will never split up.
This is my challenge.
Our family will never
split up or scatter.
Relax uncle...
I am always there for you.
Hey, Jessica.
What are you doing here?
The job's done.
When are you planning to end my game?
Isn't that what Yash said,...
...on the yacht?
Bugs.
And, not the ones that bite.
Micro transmitters. For listening.
- Listen...
- No, you listen, sweetheart.
You and Yash hired me because
you two thought I am a con woman.
That was my cover.
But I am a government agent.
I have a full brief
on your entire family.
I came here to investigate
the illegal distribution of arms.
But it was a completely
different ballgame out here.
Hard Disks.
Politicians blackmailed.
Big money.
Relax.
Your family's secrets
are safe with me.
Cheers.
Ouch!
Yash, leave.
Yash.
Stop it!
How much do you want?
Have you lost it, Yash?
You're not paying this damn woman.
Sanjana, please.
Don't behave like your brother.
Let's just get over with this.
Speak.
I want $50 million.
In bearer bonds.
Tomorrow at 12...
...leave the bag under
the Marina Lamppost.
And don't be late.
Or else it's game over for all of you.
- Sam.
- Yes, sir.
As soon as Jessica or
one of her men grab the bag...
...follow them.
Sir, here are the mortgage paper.
Please sign them.
I'll just inform the head office.
The funds will be transferred
to your account in half an hour.
Thank you.
This sucks man.
- Yes, Khanna.
- Shamsher sir,...
...the politicians have arrived.
Okay.
We'll be there in half an hour.
Shamshu, complete!
Complete!
You know, son.
There's a saying in Handiya.
"Nothing happens before time."
I am truly overwhelmed
today by your gesture.
This story which began years ago...
...is finally coming
to an end because of you.
What to do, Bhaiji?
Every time I look in your eyes...
...I can't help but miss my father.
I did all this for my family.
And, if I've to kill for my family...
...I won't hesitate.
Come on.
Sikander deserves all the praise.
He's pure gold.
Pure gold.
I wish he was my son.
History has a bad habit, Raghu.
It always repeats itself.
Poor son died the
same way his father did.
Brother must be really happy
to finally meet his son today.
God bless their souls.
Let's go, Raghu.
The politicians must be waiting.
"Sweety..."
All good, dad.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Please stand up.
Some time back, my nephew Sikander...
...whom I loved like my son...
...unfortunately died in a car accident.
One minute of silence, please.
Thank you, gentlemen.
But the show must go on.
Please be seated.
I'll come straight to the point.
In exchange for the videos...
...I want 25,000 sq.
ft of sez area in each of your state...
...where I can ship
my arms as well as drugs.
- What is he talking about?
- Cocaine.
Meow Meow. MDMA.
Mandrakes.
Etcetera. Etcetera. Etcetera.
Come, kiddo. Come.
Meet, Rana. My new business partner.
Come.
Only fools butt heads
in a profitable business.
Isn't it, Raghu?
Give them the details of the deal.
Everyone knows that
drugs are very harmful.
But their demand keeps
rising at 300% every year.
Just imagine the amount
of money we can make.
And you'll get $50 million
every year for this job.
Yash.
Now you take over.
Show them this hard disk.
It will make it easier
for them to make a decision.
Come, come.
Rana, let's celebrate our
business partnership together.
Sikander.
Mom.
My son.
By the time you get this tape,...
...you would've turned 25.
I have faith in my blood.
You'll fulfill the
task that I will give you.
Your father wasn't killed
by any politician of Handiya...
...in fact he was murdered by
our distant relative Shamsher Singh.
The same Shamsher Singh...
...whom your father
treated as his brother.
I was pregnant when
your father passed away.
Pregnant with Suraj and Sanjana.
I trusted Shamsher
Singh and came to Al Shifa.
After Suraj and Sanjana were born,
I found out that...
...Shamsher Singh was the mastermind
behind the entire conspiracy.
Now he's slow poisoning me.
But before I die,
I've made an impenetrable Will...
...so that Shamsher Singh
cannot harm my children.
You're the eldest of your siblings,
Sikander.
I entrust you with the responsibility
of saving our family.
My blessings are with you.
How did this video
get on this hard disk?
How?
Yash!
Sit down.
Sit down!
Now that you know that
you're not my children.
I'll tell you I did this for my child.
My kid.
My real son...
Is Yash.
- Lets go
- I am going to kill you guys.
Both of you.
I am going to kill you.
By signing the mortgage papers
you've already failed your mom's Will.
For me, you'll are finished.
We're so unfortunate.
We treated our brother like an enemy.
And our real enemy as our father.
Missing your brother, are you?
Why don't I send you two to him?
Suraj!
I am really missing Sikku today.
I wish brother was here...
You wished...
God protects you and
keeps you from all harm.
Missed you, bro.
- We missed you.
- Missed you too.
I can't leave you two
alone for even a moment.
Why do you look so surprised?
Did you see a ghost, bhaiji?
Give me some time.
All my life I called you Bhaiji.
It will take some
time to call you rascal.
Rascal.
I've known the truth
for the past 10 years.
And in these 10 years...
And every day,
every moment, I died many deaths.
Every time you caressed my cheeks...
...it would remind me how
my mother suffered to death.
Every time you sang...
...it would remind me
how you killed my father.
And whenever you hugged me...
...it would remind me...
...how you kept us,
brothers and sister, apart.
And you...
...let your father's love corrupt you.
Sikander...
...there are two ways.
First...
When your kin makes a mistake,...
...you leave him.
Second...
Even if your kin makes a mistake,...
...don't ever leave him.
And you decided not to leave him.
Your job is to take
revenge for your family.
And my job is to protect my father.
Wait...wait...wait...
Son...stop this stupid melodrama.
Sikander knows...
I never do anything without insurance.
What have you done, Raghu?
It contains 50 grams of gelatin...
...and I've already
pressed the detonator.
I know.
Sexy uncle.
I've been looking for an opportunity
to repay your father's debts.
And today I got one.
And for the first time, you
addressed this man by his right name.
Rascal.
Sikander.
He was offering you paradise.
- But you kept chasing after hell.
- Raghu!
- Let's go together.
Is this what you call insurance?
This wealth, the weapons, drugs!
I see... And for you?
Family. Humanity. Love.
Go.
Cover from all sides.
Team 2; Z-formation.
Block him. Block him.
All eyes on Sikander.
So what were you saying?
I should avenge my family.
And you'll protect your father.
So protect your father.
This is the time, bro.
Why did you save me?
What you did to us was wrong.
In fact very wrong.
But you did it to
win your father's love.
But I know...
...you must be feeling worse than me.
And what's the point
in punishing someone...
...who has already
realized his mistake?
Never again.
Come on.
Remember what I said.
Our family will never
Break up or split.
There's another thing I said to you.
I will send you back to your home.
With respect, to Handiya.
Take him.
Son, this isn't over yet.
I know.
But your chapter's over.
Take him outta here, baby.
There's still time.
I know you all have a
lot of doubts in your mind.
And questions too.
Bring it on.
How did you do this?
I mean how did you know that...
...that Yash has planted Jessica.
Because Suraj and Sanjana
were never so close to me to know...
...that I always hide a
spy cam along with the money.
Bad habit,
but now I'll take another name.
Shoot.
And that name is Yash.
But that hard disk was always with me.
Fake hard disk.
And what about the money that
Jessica blackmailed us for.
Cheers.
Jessica's money is now
back along with Jessica.
I have an offer for you.
This is Johnny's hard disk.
- And you must unlock it.
- And my money?
Here is $50 million in bearer bonds.
And mom's video?
Here.
What is this?
Your mother asked me
to give you this today.
Take a look.
Sexy uncle.
What a man.
So this was your plan all along.
It was always my plan
to keep my family close.
What can I say, officer?
I've done some things
which I am not proud of.
I killed my brother,
killed my sister-in-law.
Syphoned from my own children.
Pushed my son down the wrong path.
How can a father do something
like this to own his son?
And all that for what?
Money?
Power?
But where is that money?
That power?
All that gets left behind, officer.
All of it.
Anyway...
I've heard that your wife
Shakuntala hasn't been keeping well.
She has a problem with her kidney.
And she's on dialysis.
And your daughter, Kusum, isn't it?
She wants to be a doctor.
The medical seat would easily cost
you at least 10 or 20 million rupees.
And I also heard you're
retiring in 6 months.
Think about your family.
This race isn't over yet.
Because Shamsher is still...
...alive.
So there's going to be another 'race'.
Of course.
- But...
Who will be the Sikander of that race?
The Sikander of that race...
How would I know?
- Cheers.
Cheers, Sikander.
"Race."
"R A C E."
"We'll be coming back to the race."
"I am completely ruined."
"Intoxication..."
- "I've been thinking about you."
- "We'll be coming back to the race."
"You can't imagine
what it's done to me."
"Your."
"I've been thinking about you."
"Come on."
"Everybody party hard."
"We're going to dance all night."
"Don't stop drinking
till you're high."
"Take my advice..."
"...we're gonna keep drinking..."
"...and won't stop until we drop."
"Let's go baby on the floor."
"Let me love you more and more."
"I can feel my breath..."
"...you're right here and so am I."
"It's not as important as you think."
"This is your chance,
to prove yourself."
"Celebrate all you want tonight."
"Tomorrow you're mine."
"Drink till you drop."
"Sweetheart..."
"Sweetheart...
since I got high on you..."
"...you can't imagine
what it's done to me."
"Sweetheart...
since I got high on you..."
"...your beloved's completely ruined."
"Lord hear my plea..."
"I am completely ruined."
"In your love."
"Lord hear my plea..."
"I am completely ruined."
"In your love."
"I've been thinking about you."
Let the party go on-and-on."
"I Found Love."
"I found it in you."
"The intoxication in the air..."
"...is getting me high."
"I just touched it with my hands..."
"...to believe its right."
"You're my obsession,
my intoxication, and my desire."
"My fascination is to get rid of you."
"There's no way for you to run..."
"...I have my eyes on you."
"I want to ruin you,
and that's my resolution."
"Sweetheart..."
"Sweetheart...
since I got lost in your eyes..."
"...you can't imagine
what it's done to me."
"Intoxication..."
"...you can't imagine
what it's done to me."
"Your."
"Sweetheart...
since I got high on you..."
"...your beloved's completely ruined."
"Lord hear my plea..."
"I am completely ruined."
"In your love."
"Lord hear my plea..."
"I am completely ruined."
"In your love."
"You blow my mind."
Those two fools are trying
to eliminate me from this race...
...but they don't know that the
'Champion' of this race... is me!
TorrentCounter.to - Download HD & BluRay Movies in Small Size